《纸牌屋》前情提要...
Previously on House of Cards...
通向权利的道路由虚伪和牺牲铺就
The road to power is paved with hypocrisy and casualties.
永远不要后悔
Never regret.
有人想毁了你吗
Somebody's trying to take you out.
看来是的
Appears that way.
无论是谁  他们踩到不该踩的响尾蛇了
Whoever it is, they done stepped on the wrong motherfucking rattlesnake.
你帮我和加勒特重归于好
You help me repair my relationship with Garrett.
丹和我就让资金  流向正确的方向
Dan and I here get the money flowing back in the right direction.
这样如何
How about this?
我让印第安人事务局调查你们两个
I get the BIA to investigate both of you.
你指戳我们  自己也自身难保
You implicate us, you implicate yourself.
他把这个发给报社了 这是你吗
He sent them this. Is that you?
你和我都只是小卒  嘉乐威先生
You and I are just pawns, Mr. Galloway.
-不如我去告诉记者...    -亚当  闭嘴
- How about I tell the press that...   - Adam, shut up!
我们给你提供了一条出路  亚当
We're giving you an out, Adam.
如果你选择不接受的话 我会毁掉你
And if you choose not to take it, I will bury you.
我觉得冯山德背后还有更多隐情
My gut says there's more to Xander Feng than has been reported.
把时间花在这上面 比报道什么八卦性丑闻更值得
It's a far better use of my time than reporting on tabloid sex scandals.
-怕这个吗    -达奈尔!
- You scared of this?   - Darnell!
再次打击他  现在就执行
Hit 'em again and hit 'em now.
至于雷蒙德  我们快速有力地回击
We have to strike back hard and fast.
还不够
More than that.
让他受点折磨吧
Let's make him suffer.
GPS追踪警报
华盛顿特区
看看  腰果
Look at that, Cashew.
有人不听话了哟
Someone's being a bad boy.
新约圣经  以弗所书  第四章
"并且不要叫神的圣灵忧愁
"Do not grieve the Holy Spirit of God,
你们原是受了他的印记  等候得赎的日子来到
by whom you were sealed for the day of redemption.
一切苦毒  恼恨  忿怒  喧嚷  毁谤
Let all bitterness and wrath and anger and clamour,
同一切的恶毒  都要从你们中间除掉
and evil speaking be put away from you with all malice.
你们要以恩慈相待
And be kind to one another,
心存慈怜
tenderhearted,
彼此饶恕"
forgiving one another."
还要我继续读吗  还是换一本
Do you want me to keep going with this, or something else?
我无所谓
Doesn't matter to me.
我只是喜欢听你读
I just like hearing you read it.
道格  我要跟你说件事
Doug, there's something I need to talk to you about.
你说她只待几个晚上
You said that she was just staying for a few nights.
她室友把她赶出来了  她没地方可以去
Her roommate kicked her out. She doesn't have anywhere else to go.
不是我们的问题
Not our problem.
我总不能把她扔到大街上
I can't put her out on the street.
她叫什么
What's her name?
-丽萨    -姓什么
- Lisa.   - Lisa what?
你没什么好担心的
You don't have anything to worry about.
她现在在哪里
Where is she now?
在友谊会
At the fellowship.
和托儿所的一些小孩一起过夜
There's a sleepover with some of the kids from the day care.
她知道我吗
Does she know about me?
不  我什么都没告诉她
No, I haven't told her anything.
我给了你空间
I have given you space.
我信任你  瑞秋
I trusted you, Rachel,
-你却利用...    -我不会把她赶出去的
- and you've taken advantage--   - I'm not kicking her out.
弗·安德伍德  速来白宫  中国出现危机
我本可以什么都不说  但我告诉了你
I could have said nothing, but I told you.
我得走了
I have to go.
下次我们再说话前  她最好走人
She better be gone by the next time we talk.
先生
Sir.
怎么这么久才来
What took you so long?
我五分钟内就能整理好基本情况
I can have a briefing ready in five minutes.
不用了  我让赛斯去做了
Don't bother. I had Seth do it.
他没有安全许可
He doesn't have security clearance.
现在有了
Well, he does now.
总统先生  你先
Mr. President, after you.
在我办公室等我
I'll see you in my office.
日本主权是最重要的
Japanese sovereignty is a matter of precedent.
首相先生  我的忧虑越来越深了
Mr. Prime Minister, my concern is escalation.
隶属美国太平洋司令部的太平洋舰队  司令部设在日本的横须贺港
我只需要第七舰队的一小部分
Well, I'm asking for a small portion of the 7th Fleet.
我们必须让中国认清局面
We must bring China into line.
向中国展示  日美联盟坚不可破
Show them that the U.S. and Japan maintain a strong alliance.
你直接和北京方面联系过吗
Have you reached out directly to Beijing?
他们拒不承认该岛属于日本
No recognition that the island belongs to Japan.
我得和我的团队讨论一下  拟订一个计划
Well, I'd like to speak to my team and formulate a plan.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
谢谢  首相先生
Thank you, Mr. Prime Minister.
上将  给后入会的解释一下
Admiral, for those catching up...
大概六小时前  两艘中国驱逐舰进入了
Two Chinese destroyers entered waters
与那国岛附近方圆三英里的水域
within three miles of Yonaguni Island here,
也就是这里
approximately six hours ago.
可以看到该岛离台湾很近
See how close the island is to Taiwan.
这与钓鱼岛的僵局性质不同
This is different than the standoff over the Senkaku Islands.
可能是为航线的事
It could have to do with shipping routes.
或者贸易战  柿子总是捡软的捏
Or the trade war. They can't pick on the big kids,
所以他们对实力较弱的下手
so they're picking on the little one.
-看到了吗    -什么
- Do you see that?   - What?
小巷里  二号机
In the alley, camera two.
全体注意  白人男子
All posts, white male,
帽衫  帆布袋
hooded sweatshirt, duffel bag.
法尔大街东南侧
Southeast side of Fair St.
放下包
Put down the bag.
放下包  把手放在头上
Put down the bag and place your hands on your head.
站住别动
Stay right where you are.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood?
可以请你下楼来吗
Will you come downstairs, please?
弗兰西斯在哪
Where's Francis?
他在白宫耽搁了  有个紧急会议
He got delayed at the White House, there was an emergency meeting.
出什么事了
What's going on?
我会在安全屋做解释
I'll explain in the safe room.
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译 某豚   香茗小焙   葉某人
翻译 小饭   痒痒   卫老哥
蓝光版调整  timhal@HDWinG字幕组   后期 饿得慌
顾问 老杜   校对 草草   总监 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻译 HDWinG字幕组修正 请勿去掉制作者信息
《纸牌屋》
第二季  第十集
第七舰队在关岛附近吗
The 7th Fleet is near Guam?
北面90英里
Ninety miles north.
一周内就能派舰只去与那国岛
We could have ships to Yonaguni in less than a week.
但仅仅向是那个方向行进
But even sending them in that direction
都会被中国卫星发现
will be picked up by the Chinese satellites.
我们必须和盟友保持统一战线  这毋庸置疑
Well, we have to stand with our allies, that can't be in question.
如果我们不派遣舰只  而是发表声明
What if we don't send ships, just make a strong statement
强烈谴责中国擅入日本领海
condemning their excursion into Japan's territorial waters.
我们得给中国足够的压力
We still have to offer the Chinese an incentive
让他们召回驱逐舰
to call back their destroyers.
不论采取什么措施
Whatever overtures we make,
要做好应变计划
I'd like to have contingency plans in place.
已经在起草  先生
Already drafting them, sir.
凯茜  通过外交途径联系北京方面
Cathy, open up a diplomatic channel with Beijing.
看看是否有具体要求
See if there's a concrete ask,
如果没有  就提供一些选择
if they don't have one, let's create a list of options.
这就去办  先生
Right away, sir.
同日本海军的协调如何了
How about coordination with the Japanese navy?
去吧  暂时不要把我方海军牵扯进去
Go. Don't engage with our navy yet.
我要直接和御城首相对话
I want to talk directly to Prime Minister Oshiro
表达我们的意思
and express our intentions.
前海军陆战队员
Former marine.
他出现在警戒线附近  拿着一个
He showed up at the outer perimeter with explosives
装满爆炸物的包  身上也绑着炸药
in a duffel bag and strapped to his body.
天呐
Jesus.
我们逮捕了他  媒体没得到风声
We apprehended him. The press isn't aware.
很好  别走漏风声
Well, let's keep it that way.
他宣称对寄去国会大厦的
He claimed he was responsible for sending
装有白色粉末的邮件负责
the package of white powder to the Capitol.
那么这回他打算对我动真格的
So this time he really wanted to take me out for real.
不能算是
Not exactly.
他妻子上周背着他堕胎了
His wife got an abortion last week without telling him.
天呐  是针对我
Oh, my god. It was me.
对  你是目标
Yes, you were the target.
请你和我们留在楼下  安德伍德夫人
We'd like to keep you down here with us, Mrs. Underwood,
直到我们确定他是单独行动
until we can confirm he was acting alone.
我留下陪你
I'll stay.
不  你得回白宫去
No. You have to get back to the White House.
我可以在家办公
I can work from here.
弗兰西斯  我没事  真的
Francis, I'm fine. Honestly.
我就待在这儿
I'm just gonna be in here.
你要时刻陪着她
I want you to stick with her at all times.
有任何事都通知我
Keep me informed of everything.
他马上就下班了  先生
He's almost done with his shift, sir.
我可以安排别的探员
I can put another agent on--
不  我就要密查姆
No, I want it to be Meechum.
一定  先生
Absolutely, sir.
需要我待多久我就待多久
As long as necessary.
我尽快回来
I'll be back as soon as I can.
没事的
It's OK.
别去加州
Don't go to California.
我还想连任呢
Be nice to be reelected.
你会赢的
You're gonna win.
如果我不在选民前露面就不会
Not if I don't give the voters more face time.
你什么时候纹的
When did you get it?
在军队的时候
The Army?
是
Yeah.
那之后又添了些
It's grown since then.
和我说说
Tell me about it.
不
No.
为什么不
Why not?
我不想说
I don't want to.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
和我说说这个纹身
Tell me about the tattoo.
这不公平
That's not fair.
那又怎么样
So what?
你觉得让我湿了我就什么都会说吗
You think you can just get me wet and I'll spill everything?
我不是觉得
I don't think so...
我知道你会
...I know so.
告诉我
Tell me.
我喜欢那种疼痛
I like the pain.
针扎的疼
Of the needle?
对
Yeah.
有多疼
How bad did it hurt?
非常疼
It hurt a lot.
你喜欢疼痛
You like when it hurts?
我杀过很多人
I killed a lot of people.
什么
What?
在军队的时候
In the Army.
疼痛
The pain...
对我有帮助
...it helped.
继续
Finish.
我只能找到他开第一家工厂时
The most I could find was some wrangling with the EPA
和环保局的一些争端
when he opened his first plant,
但那都是40年前了
but that was almost 40 years ago.
我们需要更多
We need more.
我要塔斯克消失
I want Tusk gone.
我和道尔会继续查的
Doyle and I will keep looking.
你到现在还什么都没找到
If you haven't found anything now,
你怎么知道你能找到
what makes you think you will?
或许我们忽略了什么
Maybe we missed something.
我觉得没有  但可以再试试
I doubt it, but we could try.
你以为塔斯克此刻不是在谋划下一波进攻吗
You think Tusk isn't planning his next attack even as we speak?
我们查得很彻底  先生
We've been thorough, sir.
他从来不留痕迹
He doesn't leave footprints.
要改变策略吗
You want to shift tactics?
那赌场  我们尽快曝光
The casino. We go public as soon as possible.
你说那是万不得已的办法
You said that was a last resort.
赛斯  想个办法
Seth, you need to find a way
曝光赌场  又不会扯上我们
to make that happen so it doesn't link back to us.
如果我们点了这把火
If we launch that missile,
可能会烧到我们自己
it could blow us up too.
如果我们控制好就不会
Not if we spin it right.
-如果我们集中在...    -赛斯
- If we keep the focus on--   - Seth.
你是来听的  不是来出谋划策的
You're here to listen, not contribute.
我要是不想他出谋划策就不会让他来
I wouldn't have him here if I didn't want him to contribute.
先生  他接手才三小时
Sir... he's been sitting with this for three hours.
我已经研究了三个月
I've been working on it for three months.
而什么都没实现
And accomplished nothing.
我们该进攻了
It's time we go on the offensive.
你有什么办法
What do you think?
艾拉·萨伊德
Ayla Sayyad.
她已经在查塔斯克和冯了
She's already digging into Tusk and Feng.
她知道多少
How close is she?
她从没提过赌场
She never mentioned a casino,
但现在我知道要害在哪
but now that I know what the dots are,
我可以让她把一切联系起来
I can see that she's starting to connect them.
五角大楼还没有发言
The Pentagon isn't talking yet.
我猜他们在等白宫
I imagine they're waiting on the White House.
我听说从昨晚起他们就在
I hear there have been regular meetings
战况室频繁开会
in the Situation Room since last night.
我过会儿打给你
Let me call you right back.
-你好    -你好琳恩  我是艾拉
- Hello?   - Hey, Lynne, it's Ayla.
我刚发给你张照片
I just sent you a picture.
收到了
Yeah, I got it.
这是什么意思
What does it mean?
有点奇怪
It's strange,
说不太通啊
it doesn't really make sense.
告诉我
Tell me.
字面翻译应该是"追随货币"
"Pursue currency" would be like the most literal translation.
或者"追随金钱"
Or "pursue money."
跟踪资金
Follow the money?
这么说也行
That could work.
谢谢  琳恩
Thanks, Lynne.
我喜欢你的新布置
I like what you've done.
沙发是新的吗
This sofa, it's new?
还有这些灯
These lamps as well?
我做了些改动
I've made a few changes.
太熟悉一个地方
You get so used to a place,
再小的改变也会很显眼
the smallest things stand out.
抱歉我没能更快答复你
I apologize for not being responsive sooner.
我最近都在忙中期选举
I've been focused on the midterms.
你不用向我解释
Oh, there's no need to explain.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood,
你知道我多么尊敬你的初衷
you know how much I respect your intentions,
但我经过深思熟虑  还是认为
but I've thought deeply about this and
我不能联署现在这份法案
I can't cosponsor the bill in its current form.
民事监管的提议太过极端
Civilian oversight is too extreme a step,
不过我愿意重新考虑
but I'd be happy to revisit some of
不那么极端的提议
the other less extreme proposals.
你认为我们太极端吗
You think we're being extremist?
我也想在这件事上出力
I want to help with this issue,
但这份法案要经过...
but this bill goes through--
这份法案要通过三军委员会
This bill is through Armed Services.
进入辩论指日可待
This bill has a date on the floor.
几乎众议院所有的女性
Almost every woman in the House
都支持这份法案
supports this bill.
而我不能成为其中之一
And I can't be one of them.
你骗了我们
So you lied to us.
我没有
I didn't lie.
我没有撒谎
我想帮你们
I want to help.
只要我们重新考虑部分措辞
As long as we rethink some of the language.
你是不是因为嘉乐威丑闻的事
Are you trying to distance yourself from us
刻意和我们保持距离
because of the Galloway scandal?
不是
No.
也许你认为和我合作
Maybe you think it hurts your chances
会对你谋求连任不利
of reelection if you associate with me.
不是因为这个
That's not it.
是因为我打心眼里不赞同这种方式
It's because I honestly don't believe in this approach.
你意识到这会让外人怎么看吗
Do you realize the message this sends?
你是国会两党唯一一位女性领导人
The only woman in congressional leadership in both parties,
而你选择退出
and you bow out?
如果法案真能进入辩论
If the bill goes to the floor as is,
我不会单单退出
I won't just bow out.
我会积极反对
I'll actively fight it.
你从未问过我的立场
You never asked my position.
你只是假设
You assumed.
我真无法相信你会是什么立场
I can't imagine what that position must be.
我曾在战区服役
I've served in war zones,
我对这事的重要性有亲身体会...
I know firsthand how important--
我们现在谈的不是战区
We're not talking about war zones.
而是性侵犯
We're talking about sexual assault.
如果让特别军事法庭
How about a military commission
审查内部机制呢
to review the internal mechanisms --
我们不需要更多研究  我们需要改革
We don't need more studies. We need reform.
等我从加利福尼亚回来以后
Well, let's continue this conversation
再继续今天的对话吧
when I return from California.
我后天回来
I'll be back the day after tomorrow,
但愿你会改变想法
if you change your mind.
我不会
I won't.
但我希望你会
But I hope you change yours.
中国认为我们觉得可以收买他们是种侮辱
China was insulted at the notion we could buy them off.
需要我再联系钱主席吗
Well, do I need to call President Qian?
我看他不会与他的部长意见相左
I doubt he would contradict one of his ministers.
看看他是否愿意一对一谈
See if he's willing to talk one on one.
你得知道  先生
You should know, sir,
日本也正准备
Japan is also preparing
调遣三艘驱逐舰和一艘轻巡洋舰
to deploy three destroyers and a light cruiser.
他们在加大赌注
They're upping the ante.
让海因斯大使联络日本首相
Have Ambassador Hines get in touch with the prime minister,
看日本能否暂时按兵不动
and ask if Japan will hold off
让我先和北京取得联系
until I make contact with Beijing.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
你休息过吗
Have you gotten any rest at all?
没  你呢
No, have you?
还没
Not yet.
克莱尔怎么样
How's Claire?
特勤局认为是孤立事件
Secret Service thinks it's an isolated attempt,
但他们加强了防备
but they're being cautious.
经过嘉乐威的事和电视采访
After the Galloway thing and the interview,
半数国民当她是婴儿杀手
half the country thinks she's a baby killer,
或出轨者  或两者皆是
or an adulterer, or both.
但克莱尔挺坦然的
But Claire's taking it in stride.
我们没事的
We're in good hands.
真是太可怕了
That's very frightening.
怪不得你无暇休息
I can see why you haven't slept.
我们有一人得休息会儿
One of us should,
还是做决策的那个休息吧
probably the one that's calling all the shots.
不用  我可以再坚持一会儿
No, I can hold out a little while longer.
别  回宅邸吧  去陪陪你妻子
No, go to the residence, spend some time with your wife.
回来后会感觉焕然新生
You'll come back feeling like a new man.
说真的
Honestly, it's...
这里的压力反而更小
less stressful here.
咨询没效果吗
Counseling hasn't helped?
不是  慢慢在起效吧
No, it has... slowly.
琳达辞职的时候
I got rid of Christina
我也开除了克里斯蒂娜
when Linda resigned.
我听说了
I heard.
情况多少改善了一些  但是...
It's improved things some, but...
还需要努力
...there's still work to do.
但是想想都让我觉得累
Makes me tired just to think about it.
你应该不是第一位
Well, you probably wouldn't be the first president
在这几个沙发上打盹的总统
to get a little shut-eye on one of these sofas.
我在开玩笑呢
I was joking.
我没有
I wasn't.
行行好  休息一下吧
Do the free world a favor and get some rest.
我先出去了
I'll let you be.
不用  待在这儿吧
No, stick around.
如果钱主席
You should be nearby
打电话来  你也该在场
if President Qian wants to get on the phone.
我一向讨厌睡眠的必要性
I've always loathed the necessity of sleep.
它跟死亡一样  能让最强大的人倒下
Like death, it puts even the most powerful men on their backs.
特区豪车巴士租赁
DC Limo and Bus Rental.
这里是阿道希赌场的出行部
I'm calling from the Adohi Casino's travel department.
我们有公司账户
We've got a corporate account.
我看看
Let's see...
抱歉  我们记录里没有
Yeah, I'm sorry, we don't have one in our records.
我的错  我一定是打错电话了  谢谢
My mistake. I must have called the wrong limo service. Thank you.
密苏里巴士豪车
Missouri Bus and Limo.
这里是阿道希赌场的出行部
I'm calling from the Adohi Casino's travel department.
你不是达林
You're not Darlene.
不是  达林请病假了
No. Darlene is out sick.
由我代班  我叫帕姆
I'm filling in for her. My name is Pam.
我能为你做什么  帕姆
How can I help you, Pam?
我们明天要接待来自中国的航班
We've got a flight coming in from China tomorrow.
我们需要车
We'll need some transportation.
有多少乘客
How many you got coming?
我手里没有乘客名单
I don't have the manifest right
照常吗
The usual?
没错
That's right.
那就是一辆豪华巴士
So a luxury bus.
能坐多少人
How many does that fit?
55人
55.
通常拉20个人左右
Usually about 20 come in.
-空间应该足够了    -太棒了  谢谢
- Should be plenty of room.   - That's great. Thanks.
你觉得她是真心不认同
Do you think it's really her conscience,
还是因为法案太有争议
or because the bill is controversial?
如果她只是想避免争议
I don't think she would have threatened to fight us
就不会说要积极反对了
if all she wanted to do was avoid controversy.
我去跟她谈
I'll talk to her.
我真的很希望这个法案能通过
I really want this bill to pass.
我知道  我也是
I know you do, so do I.
我们现在非常需要杰姬  弗兰西斯
We need Jackie more than ever, Francis.
我现在成坏女人了
I'm damaged goods,
就因为亚当那事
this whole Adam thing.
不  你不是
No, you're not.
我们一起挺过去了
We fought past that.
还是有很多人相信那确有其事
Well, there's plenty of people who still believe it's true.
我们会度过这一关的  我发誓
We'll get it passed, I promise.
不  谢谢
No, thanks.
得了
Come on.
我自己抽没意思
It's no fun doing it alone.
我们可以去跑跑步
We could just go for a run.
死亡威胁平息前  不能再去跑步了
No more runs until the death threats die down,
这是新规则
that's the new rule.
但他们让你去办公室了
But they let you go to the office.
因为我坐的是防弹车
Because I was in a bulletproof car.
那这样一来我们是没戒烟了吗
Does this mean we've officially not quit?
我们向来不会轻言放弃  不是吗
We've never been quitters, have we?
先生  安德伍德夫人
Sir, Mrs. Underwood,
很抱歉打扰你们
sorry to interrupt.
我要回家了
I was gonna head home,
但如果你们想让我留下  我就留下
but I'll stick around if you want me to.
不  你已经熬很久了  去睡会儿吧
Oh, no. You've been up long enough. Get some sleep.
我明天一早就回来
I'll be back first thing in the morning.
谢谢你今天照顾我
Thank you for looking after me today.
我的荣幸  女士
My pleasure, ma'am.
先生  安德伍德夫人  再见
Sir, Mrs. Underwood.
他非常尽忠
He's very dedicated.
确实
He is.
很难找到艾德华这样的人
It's rare to find someone like Edward.
怎么了
What?
你从没直呼他名字
You never use his first name.
是吗
Oh, did I?
我觉得这样谈论她不太好
I don't feel right talking about her like this.
就是...严格讲  她现在是我上司
It's just... technically, she's my boss now.
有规矩的
There's a certain protocol.
这是道格下的命令
This is coming directly from Doug.
也就是说是副总统下的命令
Which means it's coming directly from the vice president.
我见到过几次丹顿先生
I have seen Mr. Danton around from time to time.
你知道他跟议员女士在商讨什么吗
Do you know what he and the congresswoman were discussing?
不知道  都是私人会面
No, they were private meetings.
你有预约日程表吗
Do you have the appointment schedule?
我想看看日期
I'd like to look at the dates.
不是正式约会
These weren't formal appointments.
他就是顺路来看看
He just stops by.
大多数都是晚上很晚的时候
Most of the time pretty late at night.
沃克
冯
塔斯克
安德伍德
拉尼根
钱是不是从中国来的
Did the money originate in China?
钱来自部落收入
The money came from tribal revenue.
我们的联邦选举委员会报告上写得很清楚
As our FEC reports clearly stated.
我换个说法
Let me rephrase.
这些部落收入是否来自
Did any of that revenue come from
去你赌场的中国游客
Chinese visitors who gambled at your casino?
我们有来自世界各地的游客
We have visitors from all over the world.
我只关注
I'm speaking specifically
一个叫冯山德的商人
about a businessman named Xander Feng.
我不知道那是谁
I have no idea who that is.
我查到空管局的记录显示
I'm looking at FAA flight records that show
他名下的一架私人飞机
a private plane he owns
曾多次飞抵堪萨斯城
making numerous trips to Kansas City.
我问过密苏里巴士豪车
And I spoke with Missouri Bus and Limo,
他们负责把中国游客接到你的赌场
which has transported Chinese visitors to your casino.
赛义德女士
Ms. Said--
萨伊德
Sayyad.
萨伊德女士  我回你的电话
Ms. Sayyad, the only reason I returned your call
只是因为你在《电讯报》工作
was because you work for The Telegraph.
我不是每天都能接受
It's not every day that I get a call
你们这种大报的采访
from a paper as big as yours.
但我不明白你究竟想问什么
But I don't know what you're trying to get at here,
所以如果你不介意
so if you'll excuse--
那雷蒙德·塔斯克呢
What about Raymond Tusk?
他怎么了
What about him?
冯和塔斯克有关系
Feng has ties to Tusk.
塔斯克与总统有关系
Tusk has ties to the president.
你与冯有关系
You have ties to Feng.
这看起来像是外国资金
That looks like foreign money
被用来左右政治...
being used to influence political--
你所暗示的事不仅错误
What you're insinuating is not only wrong,
而且是诽谤
it's libelous.
如果真实就不是
Not if it's true.
我会毫不犹豫地让我的律师介入
I won't bat an eyelash getting my attorneys involved.
塔斯克也这么威胁我
Tusk made the same threat.
如果一个身家四百亿的人吓不倒我
If a man worth $40 billion doesn't intimidate me,
你也吓不倒我  拉...
you certainly don't, Mr. Lan--
喂
Hello?
他挂断了
He hung up.
我和这完全没关系  雷蒙德
I had nothing to do with it, Raymond.
我在电话这头都闻得到谎言的臭气
I can smell the horseshit through the phone.
你觉得我会冒这么大的险吗
You think I'd put myself at this great a risk?
兔子急了都咬人
Desperate men are capable of anything.
我和你一样希望事情平息
I want it to go away just like you do.
那就让她停手
Then pull her back.
我控制不了媒体  雷蒙德
I have no control over the press, Raymond.
你是搬起石头砸自己的脚  不是我的  弗兰克
You'll destroy yourself, Frank, not me.
多谢你多余的忠告
Thank you for that unsolicited advice.
和道尔一起
Work with Doyle,
确保我们没有弱点
make sure we have no weak spots.
我这就打电话给他
I'll call him now.
南茜怎么说
What did Nancy say?
看来杰姬可能和敌人上床了
Well, it looks like Jackie may be sleeping with the enemy.
拉尼根说我们有诽谤的风险没说错
Lanagin is correct in saying we run the risk of libel.
他们之间的联系是有事实依据的
These links are supported by fact.
都是单线  你不能连成圈
Individually, but you can't complete the circle.
我不是说我们要大标题写
I'm not saying the headline should read:
"洗钱黑幕揭秘"  加大惊叹号
Money Laundering Scheme Exposed! Exclamation point.
只是把我们已知的情况原样呈现
Just that we present the landscape as we currently know it.
我们主要是一家财经报纸
We're first and foremost a financial paper.
很多读者都崇拜雷蒙德·塔斯克
Many of our readers worship Raymond Tusk.
那我们就该保护他吗
So we just protect him?
我们不能暗示我们无法证实的联系
We don't insinuate connections we can't back up.
有任何诉讼的机会
If there's any basis for litigation,
他的团队肯定不会放过
you can be sure his team will be aggressive.
他们以前也曾让报社破产
They've bankrupted papers before.
我觉得你应该慢慢来
I think you should slow down and take your time.
什么时候你有了完整的故事
When, and if, you have a story--
马克斯菲尔德先生
Mr. Maxfield,
雷蒙德·塔斯克打电话过来
Raymond Tusk is on the line.
你给他打电话了吗
Did you put in a call to him?
昨天
Yesterday.
他指名要找你  先生
He's specifically asking for you, sir.
我们和拉尼根通话还不到半小时
We got off the phone with Lanagin less than 30 minutes ago.
说明拉尼根立刻打电话给塔斯克了
That means that Tusk was the first call Lanagin made.
告诉他我会打回去
Tell him I'll return.
你联系过白宫了吗
Did you reach out to the White House?
他们在明天总统的新闻发布会前
They're not talking to anyone until after the president
不接受任何采访
does his press briefing tomorrow.
好吧
All right.
把事情再详细给我说一遍
Walk me through all of this again, point by point.
华尔街电讯报  中国资金  阿道希赌场
没有搜索到相关网页
密查姆
Meechum.
我们明天再说  先生
We can talk tomorrow, sir.
不用  怎么了
No. What is it?
我想申请全职做你妻子的安保人员
I'd like to put in a request to be on your wife's detail full-time.
直到死亡威胁消失
At least until the death threats quiet down.
这很体贴
That's very thoughtful.
你不同意我是不会去的  先生
I'll only do it if you approve, sir.
你和克莱尔谈过了吗
Have you spoken to Claire?
她回来的时候说过了  她觉得不错
When she came home. She likes the idea.
那就这样做吧
Then I think we should do it.
我去告诉洛克兰探员
I'll let Agent Rockland know.
抱歉打扰  先生
Sorry for interrupting you, sir.
你没打扰什么
You didn't interrupt anything.
晚安  先生
Good night, sir.
晚安  密查姆
Good night, Meechum.
你肯定猜不到刚才发生了什么
You'll never believe what just happened.
什么
What?
密查姆走进办公室
Meechum came into the office
发现我看的东西
and found me watching something...
不是新闻
...other than the news.
不是吧
Oh, no.
他很懂规矩
He was very professional about it.
-你有没有...    -没有  我只是看而已
- Were you...?   - No, no, no. I was just watching.
真是好笑
That's really funny.
你呢  你在看什么
What about you? What are you watching?
康纳给我的视频
The video Connor gave me.
我们第一次竞选州参议员
It's our first state senate race.
我都忘干净了
I forgot about that.
我也是  今早在桌上看到才想起来
So did I, until I found it in the desk this morning.
让我看看
Let me see.
...经历过  就像我
...been there, like I have.
当然  有点德州味儿无伤大雅
Of course, it doesn't hurt to have a little Texas in them...
-老天  我们当年多年轻    -是啊
- My God, look how young we are.   - I know.
大家都很和善  很热情
Everyone here has been so kind, and so welcoming.
过不了多久她就要在克莱姆森扎根了
We'll have her rooting for Clemson before too long.
这我可做不到
That's where I have to draw the line.
你怀念和亚当在一起的日子吗
Do you miss being with Adam?
你怎么提起这个来
Where did that come from?
怀念吗  不
Miss it? No.
你肯定偶尔会怀念的
Well, you must, sometimes.
我有段时间很在乎他
He meant a lot to me for a while.
但都是过去了
But that's done now.
那你呢
What about you?
我什么
What about me?
你觉得不满足吗
Are you unsatisfied?
我们现在要时时处处小心
There's just too much at stake now.
没法信任任何人
No one we can trust.
失去了曾经的自由
We don't have the freedom we once did.
也许这样更好
Maybe it's better this way.
不会分心
No room for distractions.
我不介意牺牲
I don't mind the sacrifice.
我们选择了这个
We chose this instead.
有一件事我们可以达成一致  这儿的肋排更好吃
I think the one thing we can agree on is the ribs here are better.
他就是不把我惹火不罢休
See, he's just trying to get under my skin.
不  根本无可争辩
No, it's not even debatable...
加州之行怎么样
How was California?
很累
Exhausting.
两天里12个活动
12 events in two days.
这是金门吗
Is this the Golden Gate?
对
Yes.
我原来在那里挂了幅未建成的国会大厦蚀刻板画
I had an etching right there of the Capitol before it was finished.
花了85年才完工
Took 85 years to complete it.
这座桥建了多久
How long did it take to complete the bridge.
大概四年
Uh, about four years.
罗斯福第二次就职演说后不久通行
It opened a few months after FDR's second inaugural.
罗斯福是个能成事的人
That was a man who got things done.
信仰坚定  从不动摇
Strong beliefs. and he stuck to them.
但在必要时也会妥协
But compromised when he had to.
我猜你是来讨论克莱尔的法案的
I assume you're here to talk about Claire's bill.
那可不是什么闹着玩的项目
It's not a pet project.
两党加起来有三四十个联署人
There are three dozen cosponsors on either side of the aisle.
-这是个严肃的法案    -我不这么认为
- It's a serious bill.   - I don't disagree.
措辞可能稍显随意
Except with the language.
我可以解释我的看法
I can explain my thinking,
但恐怕不能说服你
but I doubt I'll convince you anymore--
先不提什么军队尊严
Putting aside the military's honor,
军阶等级  等等一切你珍视的东西
chain of command, all the things that you hold dear...
就考虑一个简单的事实
...let's consider one simple fact.
要不是我  你坐不进这间办公室
You wouldn't have this office if it weren't for me.
我说得很清楚  我不会做傀儡
I made very clear that I wouldn't be a puppet.
我也不想控制你
I'm not trying to pull strings,
但你好歹表现出一点感激
but you could show a little gratitude.
别的都可以
If it were anything else,
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President...
但这件事不行
but not this.
这件事必然要成功  你至多只会让好事多磨
All you're doing is making the inevitable more difficult.
并非一定会成功  克莱尔还没得到足够的支持
It's not inevitable. Claire doesn't have the votes yet.
你真想在这件事上和我们对着干
You really want to fight us on this.
我一点不想和你对着干
I don't want to fight you at all,
所以才向克莱尔建议  我们坐下来谈谈
which is why I suggested to Claire that we sit down--
我既没有时间  也没有兴趣和你讨价还价
I neither have the time nor the inclination to negotiate with you!
联署法案
Cosponsor the bill,
拉好该死的票
whip the damn votes,
这不是请求
I'm no longer asking.
那我也不会再听了
Then I'm no longer listening.
你该谢我的  可不止这间办公室
You don't have just this office to thank me for.
你如果能连任  还要为那个谢我
If you win reelection, you can thank me for that, too.
那些攻击广告可不是平白无故消失的
Those attack ads didn't just disappear on their own.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
你去问问雷米·丹顿吧
Why don't you ask Remy Danton.
顺便再问问他雷蒙德·塔斯克的事
And ask him about Raymond Tusk while you're at it.
这样的枕边对话会很有意思的
That ought to make for some very interesting pillow talk.
继续好好工作  南茜
You keep up the good work, Nancy.
好的  副总统先生
I will, Mr. Vice President.
真怀念你在身边的日子
I miss having you around,
但现在你是我的眼线
but you're my eyes and ears now,
否则我立马把你要回来
otherwise I'd steal you back in a heartbeat.
谢谢  先生
Well, thank you, sir.
你这么说  对我意义重大
It means a lot to me that you say that.
道格
Doug?
我忙着呢
I'm busy.
报道刚刚见报了
The story just broke.
他们算准了总统的新闻发布会
They timed it with the president's press conference.
帮我转接副总统
Connect me with the vice president.
政治行动委员会资金引起质疑  雷蒙德·塔斯克  中国资金  国会和白宫
第七舰队目前部署在关岛附近
So the 7th Fleet is currently positioned near Guam,
如果中国将船只
where it will remain
从日本领海撤出  第七舰队也会原地不动
if China removes its ships from Japan's sovereign waters.
我和御城首相保持着频繁的沟通
I've been in frequent touch with prime minister Oshiro,
也亲自向钱主席发出提议
and have made personal overtures to President Qian.
我对缓解紧张局势持乐观态度
And I remain optimistic that tensions will be quelled
危机不会进一步升级
without any further escalations.
现在我可以回答一些问题
So, with that, I'll take some questions.
亨利  你先来
Henry, you first.
你可以对《华尔街电讯报》的报道发表评论吗
Can you comment on the Wall Street Telegraph article--
我来之前才刚知道这件事
I was just notified of that moments before I joined you.
我还没来得及看呢  简
I haven't had a chance to read it yet. Yeah, Jane?
总统先生
Mr. President,
你能给我们讲一下你和雷蒙德·塔斯克的关系吗
would you walk us through your history with Raymond Tusk?
我是来回答关于中日关系的问题的  马克
I'm here to answer questions on Sino-Japanese relations. Mark?
报道中提到冯山德
The article mentions Xander Feng,
一位富有而有影响力的中国商人
a wealthy and influential Chinese businessman --
除非问题与我刚刚的声明有关
Unless this has to do with the statement I just made...
的确有关  总统先生
It does, Mr. President.
冯和常委有联系
Feng has ties to the standing committee
而我们目前和中国陷入僵局
and we're currently in a standoff with the Chinese.
经济上
Economically--
非常感谢各位
Thank you all very much.
我并不怕这故事的开端
It's not beginning the story that I fear,
我怕的是不知道结局将如何
it's not knowing how it will end.
现在人人都是靶子了
Everyone is fair game now,
我也是
including me.
这完全在意料之中
This is par for the course,
我们已经发现沃克总统就是如此
for what we've come to expect from President Walker.
印第安捐助者  沃克对详情闪烁其辞
如果他想卖出一辆新车
Whenever he's selling a shiny new car,
他就滔滔不绝
he can't say enough about it.
引擎坏了
The engine breaks down,
变速器不好使了
the transmission gives out,
他就开始闪烁其词  无视保修
he dodges, he ignores the warranty.
我来告诉你们
I'm gonna tell you something,
我们的保修单叫做美国宪法
our warranty is the constitution of the United States,
这张保修单是没有限制条件的
and there's no limit on that.
他得好好看看宪法
He needs to read the fine print
并且开始回答我们的问题
and start answering our questions.
赃款: 最高涉及到哪一层
如果这里确有属实的内容
If any of this is true,
那么就是国会  白宫
we're talking Congress, the White House,
以及两党都算上
both parties...
我是说如果
Now, I'm saying "If,"
但如果这钱看起来像赃款
but when it looks like dirty money,
闻上去也像赃款
and it smells like dirty money,
那肯定有人手上沾着脏东西
somebody has probably got dirt under their nails.
并没有证据表明洗钱活动确实...
Look, there's no real proof this money laundering is even--
可这其中的联系令人担忧
The connections are troubling,
尤其是安德伍德
especially Underwood.
阿道希资助民主党期间
He was the House whip the entire time Adohi were
艾拉·萨伊德  《华尔街电讯报》
他一直是党鞭
contributing to the Democrats,
现在他在总统身边工作
and he's working side by side with the president now.
总统  这事能一路牵连到白宫吗
The president. So this goes all the way to the White House?
有可能啊
It might.
这只是假设
It's hypothetical.
而且  你为了证实说法  证据都是挑拣过的
And by the way, you've cherry-picked the facts to make your case.
我没有什么说法
I'm not making a case.
我的标题是《政治行动委员会资金引起质疑》
My headline is: PAC Money Raises Questions.
也确实有疑问
And it has.
我并没有给出答案
I haven't answered those questions,
但我觉得美国人民应该知道答案  你觉得呢
but I think the American people deserve answers. Don't you?
司法部长
You can bet your bottom dollar
百分之百会介入调查
the attorney general is gonna investigate.
这事已经在媒体上引起了轩然大波
With the firestorm this is causing in the media--
我们该怎么办
What's our course of action?
作为你的法律顾问  我建议你
As your counsel, I would encourage you
在有更多消息之前不要和媒体接触
not to speak to the press until we have more information.
作为普通公民
As your average citizen,
你等的越久  看起来就越可疑
the longer you wait, the more suspicious it looks.
如果有任何的违规行为
If there's been any irregularity,
都与我没有关系
I had nothing to do with it.
你和塔斯克的友谊
Your friendship with Tusk
会让你因关连而被认为有罪
implies guilt by association.
那么我们现在是做有罪推定了吗
Are we presuming guilt before innocence?
我是个律师
I'm a lawyer,
我不做任何假设
I presume nothing.
但是舆论可没有法律学位
But public opinion doesn't have a law degree.
让我们单独说两句
Give us a few moments.
我必须建议你  如果我不在场
I have to advise you not to have any conversation
不要和任何人讨论这件事
about this matter without me present.
我了解你的建议了
Your advisement has been noted.
我就在门口
I'll be right outside.
这就是你一直没和我说的事吗
Is this what you were keeping from me?
我们应该遵照你法律顾问的建议  不应该...
We should follow your counsel's advice, and not --
告诉我  钱的事是不是真的
Tell me if it's true, about the money.
比尔不在房间里  我们可能出现各种...
With Bill out of the room, we open ourselves up to all sort of--
该死  弗兰克  这事我已经被瞒得太久了
Damn it, Frank! I've been in the dark too long on this.
到此为止了
That ends now.
我不知道任何细节
I don't know any details.
冯说如果大桥的项目通过
Feng told me if the Bridge project got approved,
给共和党的资金就会断流
the GOP would stop getting money.
我们批准了项目  资金就停了
We approved it, the money stopped.
老天爷  这样白宫和钱就有直接联系了
Jesus Christ, that connects the White House directly to the money.
不是这样的
No, sir.
你什么都不知道  过去是  现在也是
You knew nothing, you still know nothing.
如果司法部发现任何确凿证据证明外来资金...
If the DOJ finds any concrete evidence of foreign money--
那是雷蒙德·塔斯克的问题
That's Raymond Tusk's head,
不是你的  你什么都没做错
not yours. You've done nothing wrong.
牵连罪  弗兰克  你也听到了
Guilt by association, Frank. You heard the man.
如果司法部进行调查  只会证明你是无罪的
If the DOJ investigates, it will only prove your innocence.
没有人能从这种事情中全身而退
Nobody walks away from something like this without bruises.
但伤不致命
Well, bruises you can survive.
只是不知事到如今要如何避免受牵连
I just don't know how we can avoid it at this point.
如果你想加快进程  平息此事
Unless you want to accelerate the process and get rid of it.
我们可以让司法部长任命
We could always have the attorney general appoint
一名特别检察官
a special prosecutor
这主意太糟了
That's a terrible idea.
可能是
Maybe so.
鉴于我们现在的情况  弗兰克
And given where we are, Frank,
我不是很想接受你的建议
I'm not inclined to follow your suggestions.
我不是说你该这么做
Well, I wasn't suggesting it as something you should do.
只是提出一种可能
Just as a possibility.
其实  我觉得你不该这么做
No, in fact, I --I don't think you should.
我觉得这种事拖得越久越好
I think it's better to drag these things out as long as possible.
让公众对这个话题产生厌烦
Let the public fatigue on it.
直到中期选举都一直对我们构成威胁吗
And have it hanging over our heads until the midterms?
热度会消退的
It'll lose steam.
如果没有怎么办
What if it doesn't.
国防部提出要对中国南海发起
I've got the Pentagon proposing tactical drone strikes
战术性无人机袭击
in the South China Sea.
我不能好几个月纠缠在这种事里
I can't be dealing with something like this for months on end.
也许你说得对  是该任命个特别检察官
Maybe you're right then. A special prosecutor is the way to go.
我没那么说  是你说的
I didn't say that, you did.
不  我只是说让你摆脱这个问题的纠缠
Oh, no. I just meant in terms of getting it off your plate.
如果你及时汇报情况  我就不会有这个问题了
It wouldn't be on my plate if you kept me better informed.
我一直是在帮你撇清干系  先生
I have done nothing but try to insulate you, sir.
刚刚媒体对我的攻击叫撇清干系吗
Is that what you call the feeding frenzy I just went through?
我向你郑重承诺  总统先生
I make this solemn promise to you, Mr. President.
如果走到那一步  我会承担罪责
I will take the fall if it comes to that,
但不会的
but it won't.
无论你打算如何处理
However you decide to deal with this,
我认为你的直觉是对的
I think your instincts are right.
我们可能不该指派特别检察官
We probably shouldn't involve a special prosecutor.
让比尔回来
Send Bill back in.
你知道这事
You knew about this.
塔斯克是我的客户
Tusk is a client,
-但我不是什么都知道    -胡说
- doesn't mean I know everything--   - Bullshit.
你之所以能成为格兰顿-希尔的合伙人
The reason you're a partner at Glendon Hill
就是因为你知道内幕
is because you know the things nobody else does.
你想让我说什么
What do you want me to say?
是真的吗
Is it true?
我们不谈公事
We don't talk about work.
我们没在床上
We're not in bed,
而是在我的办公室
we're in my fucking office.
在这里
And in here,
你为弗兰克卖命
you work for Frank.
我只为我自己卖命
I work for no one but myself.
继续自欺欺人吧
Keep telling yourself that.
不像你  我不把自己
Unlike you, I don't peddle my goods
卖给出价最高的人
for whoever can pay the highest retainer.
我是很多老大的走狗
I'm the bitch to a lot of top dogs,
我自己很清楚也很情愿
I'm fully aware and willing,
但你比我更糟
but you're worse.
你就是弗兰克的走狗  还拒不相信
You're Frank's bitch and refuse to believe it.
不是这样
That's not true.
被我戳中了
Case in fucking point.
别转移话题  你知道这笔钱却没有告诉我
Don't turn this. You knew about the money and you didn't tell me.
尽管这事会动摇我的职位
Even though it's thrown my seat into contention.
就算钱的事属实
Let's say there was money,
我也确实知道
and let's say I did know,
告诉你有什么好处
what good would it have done?
这说明你不惜看着我输
It means you were willing to watch me lose!
我只是在尊重你提出的界限
It means I respected the boundaries that you demanded.
-不改变关系  没有特殊待遇    -这是两码事
- No changes, no special treatment.   - This is different!
现在还要开特例了吗
So now we're making exceptions?
这么重要的事情当然算特例
When it's this important, yes!
鱼和熊掌不可兼得
You can't have it both ways.
你是不是...
Were you...?
我什么
Was I what?
为了打探弗兰克的消息才上我
...fucking me to get info on Frank?
你这么想吗
Is that what you think?
我不知道该怎么想
I don't know what to think.
我对你的关心已经太多了
I care about you more than I should,
但我厌倦了总要一遍遍地说
but I'm getting tired of having to say it.
他被转移到一家联邦精神病院做评估
He's being moved to a federal psychiatric facility for assessment.
正式判刑前待在高警戒的拘留中心
then a high-security detention center until the official sentencing.
这是个好消息
Well, that's good to hear.
坏消息是  我们希望你近期不要公开活动
The bad news is we don't want you doing any public events for a while.
我的法案马上要表决了
My bill is about to go to the floor.
我必须公开露面
I need to have a public profile.
你的死亡威胁越来越严重
Your death threats continue to rise.
我们冒不起这个险
We can't take the risk.
我都不能离开家了吗
Am I even allowed to leave the house?
当然可以  但我们希望你避开人群
Of course. But we want you to avoid large crowds.
我们保护你的能力
Our ability to protect--
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President.
出什么事了
Anything wrong?
我们只是在跟安德伍德夫人汇报
We were just briefing Mrs. Underwood
她的新安保规程
on her new security protocol.
我们待会儿再说行吗
Can we actually finish this later?
当然可以
Of course.
怎么样
How did it go?
他起了疑心
He's skeptical.
要我给特莉莎打电话吗
Should I call Tricia?
不  不能让他觉得我在他背后捣鬼
No. It could look like i was trying to go behind his back.
我们只需要静观其变
We'll just have to wait and see.
我要说的都说了
I made my case.
希望他不会同意
Hopefully, he'll disagree with it.
但这可能是招错棋
But this could've been the wrong move.
不要怀疑你自己
Well, don't doubt yourself.
赛斯在过去六小时里收到了三千余封电子邮件
Seth has gotten over 3,000 e-mails in the last six hours.
电话被打爆了
The phones are overloaded.
你要完全无视吗
So you ignore all that?
我不能无视司法部
I can't ignore the Department of Justice.
我能做什么
What can I do?
等我进监狱了来探视我
Come and visit me when I'm in prison.
你不非得站在门口
You don't have to stand by that door.
放松会儿吧
Take a load off.
谢谢  先生  但我应该站着
Thank you, sir, but I'm supposed to stay on my feet.
你不说我也不说
Well, I won't tell if you won't.
要是有人为这个找你麻烦
And if anybody gives you any trouble about this,
或是为任何事找你麻烦
or anything,
他们可以来找我
they can talk to me.
夜晚真美
Beautiful night.
是啊  先生
Yes, sir.
这几天你不在身边的感觉真有点怪呢
It's been strange not having you around these last few days.
你要我回到你的安保队伍中吗
You want me to switch back to your detail?
不  你跟克莱尔在一起我很欣慰
No, no. I'm glad you're with Claire.
只是你走了我才发觉
I just didn't realize how much
我有多习惯你在我身边
I got used to your company until you were gone.
在我心中保护她和保护你是一回事
Protecting her is the same as protecting you in my mind.
喝吧
Oh, come on.
你为什么要做这个
Why do you do this?
做什么  先生
Do what, sir?
这一直让我感到敬畏
I've always been awestruck.
竟然会有人愿意为别人挡子弹
People who are willing to take a bullet for someone else.
这是我为国家服务的方式
It's how I serve my country.
为国家服务的方式还有很多种
Well, there's a lotta ways to serve your country.
这就是我的方式
And this is my way.
这瓶我还没喝完呢
Oh, I haven't finished with this one yet.
不是给你的
It's not for you.
我执勤的时候不能喝酒  夫人
I can't drink on duty, ma'am.
也不是给你的
It's not for you either.
好啦  过来一起聊聊
Well, come on over and join the party.
你还没看腻我的脸吗
Haven't you got sick of seeing my face yet?
永远不会  夫人
Never, ma'am.
敬密查姆
To Meechum,
敬他的忠诚与服务
for his loyalty and service.
敬艾德华
To Edward.
我在去我律师办公室的路上  雷米
I'm on my way to my lawyer's office, Remy.
平常这时候我已经睡了
That's not where I want to be
我并不想去那地方
when I'd usually be in bed.
我无法阻止弗兰克泄露消息
I can't stop Frank from leaking things.
是啊  但你可以让他比我们更遭罪
No, but you can make sure he suffers more than us.
我说"我们"  雷米
And I say "us," Remy,
是因为现在你也是一条绳上的蚂蚱了
because your skin is in this game now, too.
你准备否认吗
Are you gonna deny?
我当然要否认
Of course I'm gonna deny.
这件事每个步骤都是合法的
Every step of this was legal.
他们无法证明其中的联系
They can't prove the links between them.
拉尼根那边呢
What about Lanagin?
他会合作的  我们要担心的是冯
He'll cooperate. It's Feng we need to worry about.
我想个办法联系他
I'll find a way to get in touch with him.
我们还有一项优势
We do have one major advantage.
公众可以恨我
The public can hate me,
但只要克雷顿-维斯特还在盈利
but as long as Clayton West remains profitable,
我的股东们就不会在乎
my stockholders won't care.
弗兰克可不行
Frank doesn't have the same liberty.
公众舆论就可以毁了他
Public opinion can demolish him.
你得确保事态会这样发展
You need to make sure that happens.
我可以跟共和党人一起想办法
I can work with the Republicans on that.
我们也会遭人仔细审视
Well, we'll be under the magnifying glass too.
这会变成一场政治迫害
This will be a witch hunt.
那我会让他们抓到该抓的人
I'll make sure that they pick the right targets.
你要攻击领导层
What you need to do is go after the leadership.
让他们受苦
Make them hurt.
他们会为了自救背叛弗兰克
They'll turn on Frank to save themselves.
博奇  乌麦克  夏普
Birch, Womack, Sharp.
特别是杰姬·夏普
Especially Jackie Sharp.
她是他钦点的人
She's his chosen one.
雷米
Remy?
我听着呢
I heard you.
我这就行动
I got my marching orders.
就看你的了
I'm counting on you.
一定不辱使命
I'll deliver.
我们明早再谈
Let's talk in the morning.
我最看好的两个人是
The two names I like the most
贾斯汀·盖因斯和希瑟·邓巴
are Justin Gaines and Heather Dunbar.
盖因斯的资历更高
Gaines has better credentials.
但他跟政府关系太近
But he's close to the administration.
如果不是共和党阻挠
I would've made him a federal judge
我已经让他当上联邦法官了
if the GOP hadn't blocked it.
这一点很重要
That's an important point.
邓巴很勇敢  她绝对可以胜任
Dunbar's got grit. She's more than qualified.
而且没有负担
And there's no baggage there.
但她更难以捉摸
But she's more unpredictable.
如果司法部长认为她是个未知数
Well, I doubt the attorney general would have put her on his list
也不会把她提上名单了
if he thought she was a wild card.
先生  我必须说
Sir, I have to say,
我认为这一步时机不到
I think this step is premature.
我们该缓缓  看看司法部自己采取什么行动
We should hold off and see what the DOJ does on its own.
我不想这么做  比尔
I don't want to do it, Bill
但我的担心是
But my fear is this.
如果我们等着水从热升至沸腾
If we wait until the water goes from hot to boiling,
会显得我们太保守了  缺乏积极性
we seem reactionary, not proactive.
但积极也可能显得防御性太强
But proactive could also seem defensive.
就像嫌疑人在别人问之前就大喊
Like the suspect that screams "I didn't do it"
不是我干的
before anyone asks.
除此之外  我们根本没时间做准备
Aside from that, we simply haven't had time to prepare.
也许等几礼拜
Maybe wait a couple of weeks.
那就达不到目的了
That defeats the purpose.
那就等几天
Then a few days.
我要选邓巴
I'd like to go with Dunbar.
-先生    -我决定了
- Sir--   - I've made my decision.
比尔  请你将我的意思转达给司法部长
Bill, I'd like you to convey my wishes to the attorney general.
最终还是得由他决定
Ultimately, the decision is his.
我们不能给他施加压力
We can't appear to be pressuring him.
当然了
Of course not.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
唯一比说服别人按我的意愿做事
The only thing more satisfying than
更让我感到满足的
convincing someone to do what I want,
就是故意没能说服他们
is failing to persuade them on purpose.
就像"禁止进入"标志
It's like a "Do Not Enter" Sign,
简直就是在求你走进去
it just begs you to walk through the door.
道尔对我们的初步背景调查已经进行过半了
Doyle's about halfway through our initial background check.
每位捐赠人
Every donor,
每次政治活动
every political event.
邓巴可能调查的每件事
Everything that Dunbar might be looking into.
很好  赛斯呢
Good. Seth?
我们要避免做任何正式声明
We avoid any official statement,
听总统的指令
follow the president's cue.
同时  我想打几个非正式电话
In the meantime, I'd like to make some off the record calls.
透露说你乐于接受调查
You welcome the investigation,
这样做是对的  等等
it's the right step, et cetera.
让民众了解你的个人看法
Give folks the personal touch.
没问题  只要不显得我们防御性太强
That's fine, as long as we don't come off defensive.
让我看看你要给谁打电话
I'd like to see a list of who you'd be calling.
有些人可能会很忙
Some of this is gonna be on the fly,
如果能让我自由发挥会更好
it'd be great if I had a little leeway.
让赛斯干他的  道尔的事就够你忙的了
Let Seth do his thing, you'll have your hands full with Doyle.
我事后告诉你我都打给谁了
I'll let you know who I've called.
好  工作去吧
All right, let's get to work.
先生
Sir?
什么事
Yes, what is it?
我知道你要委派任务
I understand that you need to delegate,
但你当着赛斯的面反驳我
but when you contradict me in front of Seth,
会削弱我对他的控制
it compromises my authority over him.
你不能事事管着他  我们要忙的事很多
You can't micromanage, we have too much to do.
赛斯还是我们团队里的新人
Seth is still new to the team.
我要确保他在好好完成任务
I need to make sure that he's doing his job properly.
我觉得他在好好做
Well, I think he is.
我是你的故障保险  先生
I am your failsafe, sir.
但如果你不让我这么做  我就没办法了
But I can't be that if you won't let me.
是吗  道格  你是我的故障保险吗
Are you, Doug? My failsafe?
你还怀疑这点吗
Do you doubt that?
我们正在全速飞向一场飓风
We're flying full throttle into a hurricane,
你却在谈办公室政治
and you're talking office politics
而不是集中全力确保我们不会被搞垮
instead of focusing on making sure we don't get ripped apart.
你说得对  先生  我不该提这事
You're right, sir. I shouldn't have brought it up.
她还在那里吗
Is she still there?
在  我告诉她我去散个步
Yeah. I told her I was going for a walk.
道格  我知道你说过你想让她走
Look, Doug, I know you said you wanted her gone,
但你要理解  我只求...
but you have to understand that all I'm asking is --
她可以留下来
She can stay.
什么
What?
她不一定得走  她可以留下来
She doesn't have to leave. She can stay.
我相信你知道分寸
I trust you to be smart.
你能读书给我听吗
Will you read to me?
我的《圣经》在屋里
My bible is inside.
不非得是《圣经》
Doesn't have to be the bible.
随便找点你手机上的
Just pull up something on your phone.
比如什么
Like what?
《双城记》  我妈妈以前会念给我听
Tale of Two Cities. My mom used to read it to me.
那是最美好的时代
It was the best of times,
那是最糟糕的时代
it was the worst of times,
那是智慧的年头
it was the age of wisdom,
那是愚昧的年头
it was the age of foolishness,
那是信仰的纪元
it was the epoch of belief,
那是怀疑的纪元
it was the epoch of incredulity,
那是光明的季节
it was the season of Light,
那是黑暗的季节
it was the season of Darkness,
那是希望的春天
it was the spring of hope,
那是绝望的冬天
the winter of despair,
我们拥有一切
we had everything before us,
我们一无所有
we had nothing before us,
我们都将直奔天堂
we were all going direct to Heaven,
我们都将直落地狱
we were all going direct the other way."
你好
Hello?
道格  是你吗
Doug, is that you?
喂
Hello?
道格
Doug?
乔帕  道·斯坦普
是的  道格  就是你
Yes, Doug, it is you.
■
本集一开始  一个反堕胎者试图袭击克莱尔
美国建国早期
除了一些法律禁止销售能够引起晚期流产的药物之外
堕胎行为是被允许的
自从1821年康涅狄格州第一个通过了禁止堕胎的法律后
其它各州也纷纷仿效
联邦政府也在1883年通过了禁止传播避孕和堕胎工具
药物和信息的"康斯托克法"
在1973年1月22日最高法院公布"罗诉韦德案"判决结果之前
除非妊娠威胁到孕妇的生命安全  堕胎在美国全境都是非法的
■
1973年  美国最高法院9名大法官
以7比2判定德克萨斯州的堕胎禁令违宪
判决书指出  个人隐私是受到宪法保护的
而在这种保护之下  女性有自主选择是否终止妊娠的权利
这便是美国司法历史上著名的"罗诉韦德案"
这个判决并没有给关于堕胎的争论画上句号
在过去41年中  围绕着这一判决的斗争从未停止过
包括堕胎权和生育权在内的女性权益问题
不仅引起了美国社会的广泛关注和讨论
还在美国的党派政治斗争和总统选举中扮演了重要的角色
■
在美国的政治光谱中  左翼民主党多是支持堕胎的"选择派"
而共和党所代表的右翼保守力量多是反对堕胎的"生命派"
每年在"罗诉韦德案"宣判的纪念日
都会有"生命派"活动人士在华盛顿进行名为"生命进军"的大规模集会
2007年  美国最高法院判定
小布什政府的"晚期堕胎禁令"没有违反宪法
民意调查显示  目前在美国
大多数人(52%)反对不加限制的无条件堕胎
只有26%的人认为在任何情况下都可以堕胎
有20%认为任何情况下都不可以堕胎